Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Historical Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Deans
  - Diers, Donna
    - Portraits, Circa 1974-1990 (Box 24, Folder 287)
  - Fain, James, photographs, Circa 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Gilliss, Catherine, photographs, Circa 1998-2004 (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Goodrich, Annie, photographs, Circa 1931, and undated (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - Grey, Margaret, photographs, Circa 1999-2003, and undated (Box 24, Folder 291)
  - Henderson, Virginia, photographs, Circa 1970s-1996 (Box 24, Folder 292)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box 144, Folder 1420)
  - Krauss, Judith
    - Photographs, Circa 1970s-2000 (Box 24, Folder 293-294)
    - Photographs, Circa 1970s-2000 (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - Portraits, Circa 1976-1992 (Box 25, Folder 296-297)
  - Wald, Florence, photographs, Circa 1996-2005, and undated (Box 25, Folder 300)
    - "Florence Wald," digital slide show of photographs, Undated; 1
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 213U)
- Diers, Donna
  - Appointment to deanship and biographical, 1972-1973, 1983, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 301)
  - Correspondence with Jean Barrett, 1972-1984 (Box 25, Folder 302)
  - Graduation speeches, 1980-1984 (Box 25, Folder 303)
  - Photographs
    - General, Circa 1972-1980s, and undated (Box 25, Folder 304)
    - Circa 1960s-1990, photocopies from other files, Undated (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - Presentations, 1975-1983 (Box 25, Folder 306-309)
  - Presentations, 1986, and undated (Box 26, Folder 310)
  - Professional activities, awards, publicity, Circa 1972-1994 (Box 26, Folder 311)
  - Publications, Circa 1970-1983 (Box 26, Folder 312)
  - Resignation from deanship 1984, Circa 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 313)
  - Speeches, 1982-1987 (Box 26, Folder 314)
- Events
  - General, photographs, 1949, 1977, Circa 1980-2003 (Box 26, Folder 315-319)
  - AIDS Ride Team reception, photographs, Circa 1999 (Box 26, Folder 320)
  - Alumnae/i Association, board retreat, Betts house, photographs, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 321)
    - Digital photographs, 40 computer files (38 JPEG, 2 ISO)
  - Ameling, Ann, retirement party, June 7, 2003, photographs (Box 27, Folder 322-324)
  - ANCM and Diana Mason, Editor-in-Chief of American Journal of Nursing, photographs, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 325)
  - Anniversary, 10th, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 326)
  - Anniversary, 25th
    - Photographs, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 327)
    - Press coverage, Circa 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 328)
    - Program, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 329)
    - Reprints of articles, Circa 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 330)
  - Anniversary, 27th, Bixler, photographs, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 331)
  - Anniversary, 50th
    - Photographs, speeches, programs, Circa 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 332)
      - "Nursing School 50th Anniversary", 1973 June 2; 1 (Box 170)
    - Photographs, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 333-336)
  - Anniversary, 60th
    - Alumni reminiscences, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 337)
    - Photographs, programs, speeches, Circa 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 338)
  - Anniversary, 75th (includes 1998 Alumnae/i Weekend)
    - Program, 1998 June 4-6 (Box 28, Folder 338a)
    - Recordings
      - "Dialogue with Laurel Vlock, Special Guest Dean Judith Krauss", 1998 May
        - Copy 1, 1 (Box 171)
        - Copy 2, 1 (Box 172)
      - "Remembrances with the Dean", 1998 June 4
        - Original, 1 (Box 173)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 173U)
      - "A History of YSN: Lux et Veritas," by Helen Varney Burst, 1998 June 5
        - Original, 1 (Box 174)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 174U)
      - "Reflections of Three Deans," Florence Schorske Wald, Donna Diers, Judith B. Krauss, 1998 June 5
        - Tape 1
          - Original, 1 (Box 176)
          - Use copy, 1 (Box 176U)
        - Tape 2
          - Original, 1 (Box 177)
          - Use copy, 1 (Box 177U)
      - "YUSNAA Social Hour and Reception in Honor of Dean Judith B. Krauss, Unveiling of Dean Krauss' Portrait", 1998 June 5
        - Original, 1 (Box 178)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 178U)
      - "YSN: Next Horizon", 1998 June 6
        - Original, 1 (Box 179)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 179U)
  - Bellos Lecture, 2000, photographs (Box 28, Folder 339)
  - Bellos Lecture, 2001, and Wisser Tea and other events, Gretta Styles and Dean Catherine Gilliss, photographs, Circa 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 340-341)
  - Bellos Lecture, 2001, and Wisser Tea and other events, Gretta Styles and Dean Catherine Gilliss, photographs, Circa 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 342)
  - Bellos Lecture, 2003, photographs (Box 29, Folder 343-344)
  - Building dedication, 855 Howard Avenue, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 345)
  - Center for Chronic Illness Care convocation, photographs, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 346-348)
  - Center for Chronic Illness Care Journal Club, guest Robert Leonard, photographs, Circa 2002 (Box 29, Folder 349)
  - Commencement
    - 1948 commencement program and scrapbook pages, Circa 1948 (Box 142, Folder 1394)
    - 2001 commencement address (Box 29, Folder 350)
    - 2004 commencement program (Box 29, Folder 351)
  - Creative Writing Award Dinner, photographs, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 352-353)
  - ENRS conference, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 354)
  - First male graduate of Yale University School of Nursing, 1955, and men in nursing, Circa 1948-1955, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 355)
  - Flu clinic, photographs, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 356)
  - Halloween, photographs, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 357)
  - Howard Scholars, photographs, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 358)
  - Launching your career, photographs, 2001-2003 (Box 30, Folder 359-361)
  - "Leadership in Nursing Research" and "Reunion Weekend 2005," photographs and brochures, Circa 2001-2005 (Box 30, Folder 362)
  - "Learn About Your Body," presentation by Linda Pellico, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 363)
  - Midwifery conference 2004, photographs and brochures, Circa 2004 (Box 30, Folder 364)
  - Pearce, Herb, reception, photographs, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 365-366)
  - "Provence: Keynote, and Opening Remarks", 1990 March 29; 1 (Box 180)
  - "A Plain Princess," performed by Yale University School of Nursing class of 1956, proceeds to United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund, Circa 1954 (Box 30, Folder 367)
  - Reif, Barbara, retirement party, December 4, 2002, photographs, Circa 2002 (Box 30, Folder 368)
  - Registration and orientation, photographs, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 369)
  - Reunions
    - Photographs, Circa 1976-1994 (Box 31, Folder 370-382)
    - Photographs, Circa 1995-1998 (Box 32, Folder 383-387)
    - Reunions, 1998, 75th Anniversary, poster session, 1949, circa 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 388)
    - Photographs, Circa 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 389-390)
    - Photographs, Circa 2001-2003 (Box 33, Folder 391-396)
      - Oversize, Circa 2003 (Box 142, Folder 1395)
    - Photographs, Circa 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 397-400)
  - Scholarship Luncheon, first annual, photographs, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 401)
  - Sexton Scholar, photographs, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 402)
  - Sigma Theta Tau
    - Delta Mu Chapter, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 403)
    - Photographs, Circa 1970s, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 404)
  - Yale Vietnam Conference
    - General, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 405)
    - Photographs, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 406)
- Faculty
  - Biographical and professional
    - Appointments, activities, 1932-1995 (Box 34, Folder 407)
    - Burst, Helen Varney and Kathy Scott, interview by Lee Kohn (Channel 8) regarding Family Childbirth Center, Circa 1980s; 1 (Box 185)
    - Sexton, Dorothy, news article and Nightingale Tribute, Circa 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 412)
    - Tennant, Elizabeth, Ireland health care study, 1928, 1961, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 413)
    - Thompson, John Devereaux, obituary, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 414)
    - Wiedenbach, Ernestine, interview, Undated; 1 (Box 183)
  - Photographs
    - Groups and miscellaneous, Circa 1928, 1955-2002 (Box 35, Folder 415-417)
      - Oversize (Box 142, Folder 1396)
    - Leger - Melkus, Circa 1980s-1999 (Box 36, Folder 422)
    - Sexton, Dorothy
      - General, Circa 1970s-2005 (Box 36, Folder 424)
      - Retirement celebration, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 425-428)
- Faculty Publications
  - Bibliography, index cards
    - Wald, Florence, Elizabeth Bixler, and faculty A-J, Circa 1940s-1960s (Box 131)
    - Faculty K-Z, articles of miscellaneous interest, Circa 1940s-1960s (Box 132)
  - Congdon, Dixon, and Walker, "Yale School of Nursing Graduates: Career Profile and Curriculum Evaluation", 1979 (Box 37, Folder 433)
  - Erickson, Florence, "The Therapeutic Relationship of the Nurse to the Parents of a Sick Child", Circa 1962 (Box 40, Folder 453)
  - Januska, Charlotte, "Development of a Family Nurse Practitioner Curriculum", 1974 (Box 40, Folder 460)
  - Johnson, Dorothy E., "Sensory Deprivation - One Aspect of Maternal Deprivation", Circa 1962 (Box 40, Folder 461)
  - Miller, Heide, "Registering the History of Nursing", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 473)
  - Schindler, Sharon L., "Two Encounters of Mothers and Newborn: Fourth Stage of Labor and First Feeding", 1969 (Box 42, Folder 485)
  - Sexton, Dorothy L., 1993 (Box 42, Folder 488)
- Government guests, photographs, Circa 1990s (Box 45, Folder 544)
- Guest books
  - National League for Nursing Yale Convention Dinner, 1969-1975 (Box 45, Folder 545)
  - Unidentified, 1964-1971 (Box 46, Folder 546)
- History of the Yale School of Nursing
  - Anniversary, 25th, exercise, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 555)
  - Anniversary, 75th
    - Burst, Helen Varney, Yale University School of Nursing: A Brief History, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 556)
    - Committee, Circa 1998 (Box 46, Folder 557)
    - Presentation by Helen Varney Burst, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 558)
  - Archives, 1918, 1946-1998 (Box 46, Folder 559)
  - Articles on Yale University School of Nursing and nursing, Circa 1972-1983, and undated (Box 47, Folder 560)
    - Oversize, Circa 1950, 1952 (Box 142, Folder 1399)
  - Articles on Yale University School of Nursing in the 1990s, Circa 1995-1999, and undated (Box 47, Folder 561)
  - Basic program, discontinuance of, and Bixler annual report, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 562)
  - Buildings, Circa 1932-1990, and undated (Box 47, Folder 563)
  - Chronology of events, Circa 1969-1990 (Box 47, Folder 567)
  - Curtis, Marcia, "Autonomy: An Institutional Study; Yale University School of Nursing, 1923-1934," and critique, 1972 and undated (Box 47, Folder 568)
  - Deans, 1944-1949, 1978-1983, and undated (Box 47, Folder 569)
  - Educational program, development of, Circa 1932-1969 (Box 47, Folder 570)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 1926-1944 (Box 47, Folder 571)
  - Faculty appointments, Yale-New Haven Hospital budget, salaries, Circa 1936-1944 (Box 47, Folder 572)
  - First three years, 1926, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 573)
  - Glass slides and negative plates
    - American Red Cross
      - Girl Scouts taking American Red Cross course in home hygiene, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1360)
      - Home hygiene instruction, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1361)
      - Nurse instructing mothers in child care, Zloczow, Poland, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1362)
      - Nurses conduct School of Nursing in Haiti, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1363)
    - Belleview Training School, writing room, lecture hall, first head nurses, library, reception hall, 1890, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1364)
    - "Better Babies"
      - "Better Babies" in Maine, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1365)
      - "Better Babies" in the Philippines, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1366)
      - Indian "Better Baby", 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1367)
    - Buildings, floor plans, and construction drawings of hospitals, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1368-1370)
    - Clinical experience records of students, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1371-1374)
    - Florence Nightingale Pledge, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1375)
    - Graphs
      - Relationship of educational levels to nursing achievement, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1376)
      - Henry Street Organization, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1377)
      - Hospital staffing and nursing organization, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1378)
    - Harper Hospital, old operating room, 1890 (Box 140, Folder 1379)
    - Modes of transportation, Undated (Box 140, Folder 1380)
    - New York Hospital, Diet Kitchen, Circa 1890 (Box 140, Folder 1381)
    - Portraits
      - Dix, Dorothea Lynde, 1802-1887, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1382)
      - Maxwell, Anna Caroline, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1383)
    - State School of Nursing, Prague, Czechoslovakia, classroom, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1385)
    - Warsaw School of Nursing
      - Laboratory, 1923 (Box 140, Folder 1386)
      - Nursing students demonstrating the Polish Mazurka, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 1387)
  - Grace Building, move to, Circa 1990 (Box 47, Folder 574)
  - Graduate school at Yale, Yale University School of Nursing becomes, Circa 1934-1962 (Box 47, Folder 575)
  - Insignia and banner information, 1946-1966, and undated (Box 47, Folder 576)
  - International students at Yale University School of Nursing, photographs and news clippings, 1948-1960 (Box 47, Folder 577)
  - Nursing Arts curriculum, Circa 1944-1949 (Box 47, Folder 578)
  - Nursing practice at Yale University School of Nursing, 1940, 1956, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 579)
  - Objects of Yale University School of Nursing, photographs, Circa 1976-1980s, and undated (Box 48, Folder 580)
  - Photographs and Central Registry for Nurses card (with accompanying letters), Circa 1913-1917, 1978, 2002, and undated (Box 48, Folder 581)
  - Preliminary plans to establish Yale University School of Nursing, Circa 1921-1923, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 582)
  - Prizes, 1975-1987, and undated (Box 48, Folder 583)
  - Recordings, audiovisual
    - "60 Years of YSN Students", 1983 May 4; 1 (Box 205)
      Presented by students in N700 (Topics in Nursing History) to Yale School of Nursing Faculty Meting
    - "Nursing Thought and Action", 1981
      - Original, 1 (Box 206)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 206U)
    - "Yale School of Nursing 1974, A Time for Nursing", 1 (Box 207)
  - Seal and coat of arms, Undated (Box 48, Folder 584)
  - Student problems regarding professional attitudes, 1931-1932 (Box 48, Folder 585)
  - Yale-in-China, nursing activities
    - General (contains correspondence and articles from Drusilla Poole), 1936-1950 (Box 48, Folder 586)
- Humanities and art, 2000, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 590)
- Library collections on nursing
  - Adelaide Nutting Historical Nursing Collection, title list, Undated (Box 48, Folder 593)
  - Archives, correspondence regarding loans and special exhibits, Circa 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 594)
    - Restricted (Box 150, Folder 5)
      Restricted until January 1, 2073
  - Center for the Study of the History of Nursing, University of Pennsylvania, Circa 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 595)
  - Correspondence regarding historical matters, 1984-1995 (Box 49, Folder 596)
    - Restricted (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - In-house loans from Yale University School of Nursing Archives, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 597)
    - Restricted (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - J.B. Lippincott Company, Publishers, chronology of events, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 598)
  - Loan records, 1985-1998 (Box 49, Folder 599)
    - Restricted (Box 150, Folder 8)
      Restricted until January 1, 2073.
  - Mugar Memorial Library, Boston University, Nursing Archive, publications and historical materials, Circa 1968-1981, and undated (Box 49, Folder 600)
  - O'Neill Library, Boston College, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 601)
  - Palmer-Davis Library, Massachusetts General Hospital School of Nursing, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 602)
  - Palmisano-Drucker, Elsalyn, Interagency Council on Library Resources for Nursing, "Guide to Archival Sources in Nursing", 1989 (Box 49, Folder 603)
  - Presbyterian Historical Society, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Undated (Box 49, Folder 604)
  - "Registering the History of Nursing", 1992 (Box 49, Folder 605)
  - Research or reference queries regarding historical collection or Yale University School of Nursing theses, 1992-1998 (Box 49, Folder 606)
    - Restricted (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Archives, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 607)
  - Yale University Library System, Manuscripts and Archives, ORBIS search print-out, Undated (Box 49, Folder 608)
  - Yale University School of Nursing Special Collection, print-out of database as of January 1991, Circa 1991, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 609)
- Maternal-Newborn Nursing
  - Male midwives at Yale University School of Nursing, 1977-1980 (Box 49, Folder 610)
  - News clippings, Circa 1956-1978, and undated (Box 49, Folder 611)
  - Photographs, Circa 1959-1990s (Box 49, Folder 612)
  - Program at Yale University School of Nursing, flyers, Circa 1965-1985 (Box 49, Folder 613)
  - Wiedenbach, Ernestine, papers, news articles, photographs, and negatives, Circa 1955-1966, 1998, and undated (Box 49, Folder 615)
- Maternal-Newborn Nursing / Nurse Midwifery Program (Helen Varney Burst's files)
  - Articles from Morris A. Wessel, Circa 1943-1998 (Box 49, Folder 616-617)
  - Childbirth questionnaires from patients (restricted), Circa 1950s (Box 149, Folder 618-619)
  - Correspondence and photographs, newspaper clippings, Circa 1980s (Box 50, Folder 620)
  - Developments at YSN in programs of maternal and newborn health nursing and nurse-midwifery, news article, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 621)
  - Dixwell Preventative Health Program, Circa 1988-1992 (Box 50, Folder 622)
  - Fair Haven Clinic, pre-natal guide, Circa 1990 (Box 50, Folder 623)
  - Heardman, Helen, original manuscript of book, Relaxation and Exercises for Natural Childbirth, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 624)
  - International nursing, Circa 1987 (Box 50, Folder 625)
  - Journals and brochures, Circa 1982-1990 (Box 50, Folder 626)
  - March of Dimes
    - General, Circa 1977-1983 (Box 50, Folder 627)
    - Education Advisory Committee, Circa 1979-1987 (Box 51, Folder 629-630)
      Restricted until January 1, 2024.
    - Local and regional, Circa 1979-1984 (Box 51, Folder 631)
    - Nutrition internship program, Circa 1977-1988 (Box 51, Folder 632-633)
    - Region I program orientation meeting, Circa 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 634)
    - Virginia chapter, Better Births Symposium, Circa 1982 (Box 51, Folder 635)
    - Volunteer Leadership Conference, Circa 1980 (Box 51, Folder 636)
  - New Haven Family Planning Clinic
    Restricted until January 1, 2029.
    - Needs assessment reports and plans, 1986-1988 (Box 51, Folder 637)
    - Needs assessment reports and plans, 1989-1992 (Box 52, Folder 638)
    - New Haven Health Department
      - Consultation, Circa 1991-1993 (Box 52, Folder 639-640)
      - Title X, Circa 1984-1992 (Box 52, Folder 641)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles, etc., Circa 1970s-1980s (Box 52, Folder 642-644)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles, etc., Circa 1980s (Box 53, Folder 645)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles (historical), Circa 1970s (Box 53, Folder 646-647)
  - Nurse-Midwifery Week, Circa 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 648)
  - Nutrition, Circa 1960s-1976 (Box 53, Folder 649)
  - Patient data sheets (blank), statistics, and statistics handbook, Circa 1982-1988 (Box 53, Folder 653)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 142, Folder 1402)
  - Photographs, correspondence, articles, Circa 1970s-1980s (Box 53, Folder 654)
  - Program evaluations and community assessments, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 655)
    Restricted until January 1, 2030.
  - Reports, Summary Progress Report, Medically Approved Protocols and Physician-Signed Medication Orders, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 656)
    - Maternal-Newborn: Service codebook, undated; 1
  - Rooming-in
    - Development of plans and procedures for a rooming-in time study, Circa 1948-1951, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 658-659)
    - History, articles, Circa 1947-1975 (Box 54, Folder 660-661)
    - History, negatives and photograph, Undated (Box 54, Folder 662)
    - Impressions from patients, Circa 1952-1953 (Box 54, Folder 663-665)
    - Project (obstetrics), Circa 1948-1951 (Box 55, Folder 666)
  - Sex and poverty - "Sex in the Slums" by Angel Fiasche, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 667)
  - "A Social History of Washington Heights, New York City," Columbia-Washington Heights, Community Mental Health Project, Columbia University, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 668)
  - Training grant application, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 669-672)
  - Weight gain pattern, Circa 1977 (Box 55, Folder 673)
  - Women's Health Services, gynecology service evaluation, Undated (Box 55, Folder 674)
- Minorities, photographs, Circa 1970-1993 (Box 56, Folder 675-677)
  - Oversize (Box 142, Folder 1403)
- Nursing history (general)
  - Army school of nursing
    - Class of 1925, classbook with news clippings and letters, including from Annie W. Goodrich, Circa 1925-1974 (Box 56, Folder 678)
    - Reunion, 50th, news clippings, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 679)
  - Eight-hour-day for nurses, Circa 1918-1940, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 680)
  - Miscellaneous historical items, Circa 1888-1986 (Box 56, Folder 681)
  - News clippings regarding nursing education, 1940-1959 (Box 56, Folder 682)
  - Nightingale items (copies), Circa 1896-1979 (Box 56, Folder 683)
  - "Nurses are Lucky Girls!" by George Sessions Perry, from The Saturday Evening Post, 1954 (Box 142, Folder 1404)
  - Nursing shortage, 1948-1955 (Box 56, Folder 684)
  - Speeches regarding college-based nursing education, 1904, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 685)
  - Wald, Lillian, copy of 1889 letter to New York Hospital applying for admission to the School of Nursing, Circa 1952 (Box 56, Folder 686)
- Orientation
  - Faculty orientation materials, Circa 1979-1989 (Box 56, Folder 687-688)
  - "Yale University School of Nursing Orientation Manual, 1981-1982", Circa 1981 (Box 56, Folder 689)
- Pediatrics
  - Evaluations
    - Class of 1981
      - Pediatrics graduates followup, Circa 1981 (Box 56, Folder 690)
      - Six-month-out evaluations
        Restricted until January 1, 2021.
        - General, Circa 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 691)
        - Summary of evaluations, Circa 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 692)
      - Twelve-month-out evaluations
        - General, Circa 1982 (Box 57, Folder 693)
        - Returns, Circa 1982 (Box 57, Folder 694)
        - Summary of results, Circa 1982 (Box 57, Folder 695)
    - Class of 1982
      - Six-month-out evaluations
        - General, Circa 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 696)
        - Returns, Circa 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 697)
        - Summary of results, Circa 1983 (Box 57, Folder 698)
      - Twelve-month-out evaluations
        - General, Circa 1983 (Box 57, Folder 699)
        - Returns, Circa 1983 (Box 57, Folder 700)
        - Summary of results, Circa 1984 (Box 57, Folder 701)
    - Class of 1983
      - Six-month-out evaluations
        - General, Circa 1983 (Box 57, Folder 702)
        - Returns, Circa 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 703)
        - Summary of results, Circa 1984 (Box 57, Folder 704)
      - Twelve-month-out evaluations
        - General, Circa 1984 (Box 57, Folder 705)
        - Returns, Circa 1984 (Box 57, Folder 706)
        - Summary of results, Circa 1984 (Box 57, Folder 707)
    - Class of December 1983
      - Six-month-out evaluations, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 708)
      - Twelve-month-out evaluations, Circa 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 709)
    - Class of 1984
      - Six-month-out evaluations
        - General, Circa 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 710)
        - Returns, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 711)
    - Data on Pediatric Nursing Program graduates, Circa 1975-1982 (Box 57, Folder 712)
    - Employer Questionnaire, six-month-out and twelve-month-out survey, Undated (Box 57, Folder 713)
    - Profile of graduates evaluation form for six-month-out and twelve-month-out survey, Undated (Box 57, Folder 714)
    - Tables for evaluation of six-month-out and twelve-month-out data, Undated (Box 57, Folder 715)
  - News clippings, 1955, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 716)
  - Photographs, Circa 1935-1954 (Box 57, Folder 717)
  - Yale-New Haven Hospital, photographs, Circa 1940s-1950s (Box 57, Folder 718)
- Photographs, miscellaneous
  - First Nurses' Institute on Alcoholism, Yale participants, photograph, 1954 (Box 146)